[Waco] Clifton Manufacturing Company records, Inclusive: 1909-1987, undated, Bulk: 1946-1971, undated
Baylor University Libraries
[Waco] Clifton Manufacturing Company records
Inclusive: 1909-1987, undated, Bulk: 1946-1971, undated
Baylor University Libraries https://www.baylor.edu/library/
1830
Clifton, Albert L.; Clifton Manufacturing Company; Clifton, Albert T.
29 document boxes and 1 oversize box
The [Waco] Clifton Manufacturing Company records document the company located in Waco, Texas. Legal documents, clippings, correspondence, newsletters, organizational charts and reports, credit memos, photographs, and printing plates are present.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The [Waco] Clifton Manufacturing Company was established in Waco, Texas, in 1909 by Albert Turner Clifton, Henry Coffield, W. R. Clifton, and W. D. Lacy as Clifton Coffield Manufacturing Company. In 1910, Albert T. Clifton became the main proprietor and remained so until his death in 1948. He was succeeded by his son, Albert Lacy Clifton, as sole owner. Albert L. previously worked in the company as cutter, supervisor, and general manager.
The company began producing canvas products because of its proximity to local cotton fields. Items such as tents and tarpaulins, cotton sacks, and wagon covers were popular in early years while automotive seat covers were added in the 1920s and apparel in the 1930s. In the 1940s and 50s, cotton military products became a staple as Clifton Manufacturing was awarded several military contracts. In the 1960s, the company received the Quality Control Award given by the Department of Defense Supply Agency for at least five consecutive years. During this time the company also began to shift toward primarily manufacturing apparel.
On April 30, 1969, Clifton Manufacturing Company merged with Juvenile Manufacturing Company of San Antonio, Texas. By July, the company was renamed Santone Industries, Inc.
Scope and Content
The [Waco] Clifton Manufacturing Company records are reflective of the company located in Waco, Texas which operated from 1909-circa 1969 and should not be confused with the Clifton Manufacturing Company, which was located in Spartanburg, South Carolina. The South Carolina company was in operation from 1880-1970s, and their records can be found at Clemson University in Clemson, South Carolina, and Converse College in Spartanburg, South Carolina.
The Personal Series includes items from Clifton’s other endeavors such as Clifton Buick, a car dealership, and the Clifton-Simpson Furniture company. Certificates are present for philanthropic efforts as well as other legal documents, clippings, photographs, and the Quality Control Award flag presented to the company by the Department of Defense.
The Administrative series includes correspondence, legal documents, newsletters, organizational charts, marketing, and director’s reports. Also included is a building appraisal from 1968, which was done in response to the City of Waco Urban Renewal Plan. The Financial Series includes audit reports, budget and sales reports, and credit memos. In the 1960s, the longevity of the company was in question, which is notable by the number of credit memos and inventories created.
The Product Information series provides the most comprehensive look at items manufactured by the company. Product catalogs, fabric swatches, and salesmen’s books provide price ranges and advertising for items produced from 1910-1971. Fabric swatches are also available in the catalogs for a contemporary view of materials used and available, as well as the evolution of design, user, and manufacturing interests.
Photographs and Printing plates provide insight into company culture as well as products. Company events, such as annual picnics and Christmas parties, are present as well as personnel doing various jobs at the company. Photos are also representative of the products sold. They were taken to be included in catalogs and artwork and were also made into printing plates for press runs. Several local Waco photographers were used, including Fred Gildersleeve, Jimmie Willis, and Windy Drum.
Arrangement
There was no previous discernible arrangement for the collection. Some items were previously housed in 3-ring binders but have been removed to accommodate needed preservation. The collection is now arranged in five series: I. Personal, II: Administrative, III. Financial, IV. Product Information, and V. Photographs and Printing Plates.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 1830. Acquired 1978-08-00
Related Resources
Related references
“Santone Industries, Inc.” San Antonio Express (San Antonio, Texas). 1969 July 10.
“Clothing Firms to Merge.” San Antonio Express (San Antonio, Texas). 1969 April 17.
“Clifton Co. Merges with Another Firm.” The Waco Citizen (Waco, Texas). 1969 July 10.
Index Terms
Subjects
Business enterprises -- Texas -- Waco.; Canvas industry -- Texas -- Waco.; Cotton textile industry -- Texas -- Waco.; Manufactures -- Catalogs.; Patent infringement.; Patents.; Textile factories -- Texas -- Waco.; Trademark infringement.; Trademarks.
Genres
Advertisements.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Legal documents.; Newsletters.; Photographs.; Printing Plates.; Trade catalogs.
- Personal, 1909-1976, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Personal series, dated 1909-1976, includes certificates, legal documents, clippings, and photographs. Materials from other Clifton businesses, such as Clifton Buick and Clifton-Simpson Furniture Co., as well as the “Q” flag from Clifton Manufacturing, are also present. The series is arranged chronologically and in good condition.
  - Desk Plate, Albert C. Clifton, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Personal Certificates, 1909-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clifton-Coffield Manufacturing Company, 1909-1918 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Legal Documents, 1909-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Certificates, 1923 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Certificates, 1942-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clifton-Simpson Hardware Company, 1943-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1950-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clifton House Print, circa 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clifton Buick, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - “Q” Flag, circa 1969 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Providence Hospital Advisory Board, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Culver Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Equalization, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Administrative, 1921-1974, undated; 2
  The Administrative series, dated 1921-1974, includes correspondence, legal documents, employee handbooks and newsletters, organizational charts, trademarks and patents, personnel and operations policies and manuals. Correspondence includes litigation with the company Koratron on a trademark and patent infringement case and the matter of royalty payments, granted trademarks, and patents. There is also a review of trademark concerns surrounding O’Brien Manufacturing and Nev-R-Iron usage. The newsletter Slips and Tips was produced from 1943-1954 and includes important company information as well as personal advertisements, inspirational quotes, and employee news, and provides insight into the push for war bond sales and support of active-duty military by employees. Obvious concern for company longevity is present in materials from the 1960s and is represented through organizational charts, ideas, and analysis of operations and possible improvements. The series is in chronological order and in good condition.
  - Employee Benefits Posters, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Employee Handbook, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Multi-Divi [Bound, Large Number Multiplication Table], undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Supplier Address Book, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wage Schedule, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Trademarks and Patents (1 of 2), 1921-1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Trademarks and Patents (2 of 2), 1921-1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Trademarks and Patents (1 of 2), 1925-1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Trademarks and Patents (2 of 2), 1925-1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Form Letters, Credit Department, circa 1930-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Philip E. Siggers [Patent], 1932-1937 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Survey [Long-term Viability], 1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Canvas Jobbers’ Contracts, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Directory: Southern States Industrial Council, 1946-1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters: Slips and Tips, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Administrative, Greater Waco Safety Council, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Texoma Seat Covers, Inc. Buyout, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sewing Room Installation Manual (1 of 3), 1962 June (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sewing Room Installation Manual (2 of 3), 1962 June (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sewing Room Installation Manual (3 of 3), 1962 June (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Texas Safety Association, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board Directors Report, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Certificates, 1963-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Company Ideas, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Job Analysis, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - O’Brien Order Billing and Production Control Systems, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - O’Brien Manufacturing Company Trademark Concern, Nev-R-Iron, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Company Benefits Booklet, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Marketing Report and Program (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Marketing Report and Program (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Koratron (1 of 3), 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Koratron (2 of 3), 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Koratron (3 of 3), 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cost Accounting Systems Manual, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Department of Defense Quality Award, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Introduction to Clifton [Scrapbook], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - O’Brien Sales Meeting Notebook (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - O’Brien Sales Meeting Notebook (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1967 April (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Quality Award Flag, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Quality Award for Performance, Texas Senate Resolution, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Company Organization, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Quality Control Procedure, circa 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Accounts List, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Policies, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Proposal for Refinancing, 1968 May (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Company Outlook Report, 1968 August (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Correspondence Directions, 1968 October (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Clifton-Simpson Building Appraisal [Urban Renewal], 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: General, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Insurance Loan Information, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Naman, Howell, Smith & Chase [Legal], 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Remodeling Contract, Circle Lumber Company, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Urban Renewal Move, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Albert L. Resignation, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Clipping: Merger with Juvenile Manufacturing Co., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Santone, 1969-1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Employee File, Work Duties, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Office Memos and Letters, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Retirement Benefits, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce International Trade Opportunity, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Suggestion Committee, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: Clothesline, Santone Industries, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Survey of Manufacturers in Waco, Texas, Prepared by Baylor University Hankamer School of Business, 1973 March (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Goodwill, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Sewing Machine Operators Program, General, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Sewing Machine Operators Program, Needle Industry Committee, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sewing Machine Operators Program, Santone Industries, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Financial, 1917-1972; 3
  The Financial series is dated 1917-1972 and includes, budgets, sales reports, audits, credit memos, schedules, inventories, and refinancing information. The series is in chronological order and in good condition.
  - General, 1917-1925 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Audit Report, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Audit Report, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Budget and Sales Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Budget Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Budget and Sales Reports, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Partnership Return of Income, 1937-1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Budget and Sales Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Audit, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Accounting Instructions, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Budgets, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - General, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - General, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Audit, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Budgets, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Depreciation Schedule, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Cost System, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - General, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Cash Receipts (1 of 2), 1966 November-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Cash Receipts (2 of 2), 1966 November-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Credit Memos #723-800-#25901 (1 of 3), 1966 November 1-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Credit Memos #723-800-#25901 (2 of 3), 1966 November 1-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Credit Memos #723-800-#25901 (3 of 3), 1966 November 1-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Journal Vouchers (1 of 3), 1966 November 1-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Journal Vouchers (2 of 3), 1966 November 1-1967 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Journal Vouchers (3 of 3), 1966 November 1-1967 October 31 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Audit Reports A, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - [Bank] Notes Payable, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - [Bank] Notes Payable, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Journal Vouchers (1 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Journal Vouchers (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1967 November-1968 October (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Cash Receipts (1 of 3), 1967 November-1969 January (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cash Receipts (2 of 3), 1967 November-1969 January (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cash Receipts (3 of 3), 1967 November-1969 January (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Operating Statements, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Thomas A. Edison Industries, 1967-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cost Information, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cost System, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Equipment, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - General (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - General (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Nine Month Financial Statement, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Proposal for Refinancing Clifton Manufacturing, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Refinancing, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Inventory, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Payroll Bank Reconciliation, Bellmead State Bank, 1968 November 2-1969 January 31 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Accounts Payable, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Accounts Receivable Lists, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Audit: Upholstery Company, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Budget Control, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cost Information, Slacks, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Credit and Memos, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - General, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - List of Accounts, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Upholstery Company, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Inventory Trim, 1969 January 31 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Balance Sheet and Statement of Income, 1969 February (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Inventory: Finished Goods, 1969 March 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Inventory: Trim, 1969 March 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Inventory, 1969 March 28 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Inventory, 1969 April 30 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Inventory: Trim, 1969 March 29 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Inventory: General, 1969 April 30 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Inventory: Upholstery, 1969 April 30 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Credit Memos, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Miller Freight, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Aged Accounts Received, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Period Statements (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Period Statements (2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Product Information, 1910-1971, undated; 4
  The Product Information series is dated 1910-1971 and provides a comprehensive look at the products manufactured and sold by the company through catalogs, fabric swatches, inventory and price lists, and employee sales books. Product catalogs document the evolution of the company from selling canvas products such as automotive seat covers, tire covers, car roofs, and driving apparel, awnings, and tents to apparel. Sales books list products and pricing made available to wholesalers along with catalogs and flyers, personal notations, and periodic company correspondence for the salesperson. In most cases, the books overlap with the general catalogs but provide insight into individual working processes. Due to the adhesives used, some catalog sample pages are fused together, and caution should be used when handling these materials. The series is in chronological order and in good condition.
  - Catalogs: Canvas Goods, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Catalogs: Tents and Tarpaulins, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs: General [Not Clifton Manufacturing Company], 1910-1952 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs: Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1915-1918 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs: Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1919-1922 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs: Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1923—1925 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sales Book (1 of 5), 1923-1950 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sales Book (2 of 5), 1923-1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Sales Book (3 of 5), 1923-1950 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sales Book (4 of 5), 1923-1950 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sales Book (5 of 5), 1923-1950 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1926-1929 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Sales Book, F.E. Stewart (1 of 4), 1926-1931 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sales Book, F.E. Stewart (2 of 4), 1926-1931 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Sales Book, F.E. Stewart (3 of 4), 1926-1931 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Sales Book, F.E. Stewart (4 of 4), 1926-1931 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs: Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs: Awnings and Porch Curtains, 1930-1933 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs: Cemetery Tent Circulars, 1931-1934 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs: Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs: Automotive Fabric Equipment, 1934-1936 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Sales Book (1 of 2), 1934-1937 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Sales Book (2 of 2), 1934-1937 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs: Tents and Tarpaulins [Not Clifton Manufacturing] (1 of 2), 1936-1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs: Tents and Tarpaulins [Not Clifton Manufacturing] (2 of 2), 1936-1967 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Sales Book, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Sales Book, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Catalogs: Canvas Goods, 1937-1940 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sales Book, 1938-1941 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs: Uniforms and Apparel, 1938-1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sales Book (1 of 2), 1939-1955 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sales Book (2 of 2), 1939-1955 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs: Awnings, circa 1940 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sales Book, circa 1940—1949 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook: Catalog Illustrations, circa 1941 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Sales Book (1 of 2), 1941-1943 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Sales Book (2 of 2), 1941-1943 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1946-1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sales Book, 1946-1949 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Sales Book, 1947-1949 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Price List, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Sales Book, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Sales Book (1 of 3), 1952 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Sales Book (2 of 3), 1952 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Sales Book (3 of 3), 1952 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Seat Covers, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Price Lists, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs: General, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sales Book (1 of 2), 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Sales Book (2 of 2), 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Catalogs: General, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Sales Book, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs: General, 1954-1968 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Sales Book, 1955-1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Catalogs: Apron-Ette, circa 1956 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sales Book (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Sales Book (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sales Book, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs: General, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Pricing and Correspondence, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Sales Book, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs: Seat Covers, 1960-1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs: Awnings & Porch Swings, circa 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs: Tents and Tarpaulins, circa 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sales Book, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Yardage Estimates, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Tex-o-graph Readings, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - O’Brien Manufacturing Company Specifications, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Specifications ½ Boxer-Boys Student Slacks & Slacks Shorts (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Specifications ½ Boxer-Boys Student Slacks & Slacks Shorts (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Apparel Specifications, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - O’Brien Advertisements [Apparel], 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Catalogs: General, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Sample Cuts: "Come on Strong" (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Sample Cuts: "Come on Strong" (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Clifton Jeans Sample Specifications, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Sample Specifications, Clifton Slacks, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Santone Codes and Specifications [Pants], 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)